Abdulgader Alhabeel

An IT pre-graduate student and technician with +8 years of experience in setting up computers, networks, programming, computer hardware maintenance, skilled Linux administrator and Full Stack Developer. Aiming to apply and develop my skills by working in a leading company to be one of the success partners in achieving it's strategies goals through the applications of the latest technologies in the field of business.

☑ c8li@hotmail.com 📞 +966 59 689 6980 🔮 Jeddah 🛅 linkedin.com/in/abdulqader-alhabeel

EDUCATION

Arab Open University

Bachelor in Sciences - 3.2 /4

06/2017 - Present,

LANGUAGES

Arabic: Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English: Professional Working Proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

ICCSAT. co.

Technical Support Engineer

01/2016 - 01/2017

- Helping customers to solve technical issues with NMS for V-Sat.
- Installing V-Sat hardware (iDirect, Linkstar & Comtech).
- Providing 1st/2nd level support to direct clients, developing customer-facing documentation on an as-needed basis.

4N Telecommunication. Co.

Network technician 01/2017 - 01/2019

- Site installation, configuration, and troubleshooting for end users.
- Develop creative solutions and assess risks/benefits and Participate in Change Management Process.
- Installing, configuring and commissioning for wireless/V-Sat hardware.
- Knowledge of: InfiNet, Edge Core, Ubnt, Alcon, Motorola, Cambium, Memosa and all other WLAN hardware P2P connection.

Linux system administrator

01/2019 - 01/2021

- · Installed VMware ESXi software which is a part of vSphere suite on bare metal hardware and implemented several virtual hosts on top of that ESXi environment.
- Installed, monitored and managed several virtual hosts on VMware ESXi using the software vSphere client.
- Support of Applications like Apache Tomcat and Java based applications running on Linux machines for multiple clients.
- Installed Linux OS, and configured required network on the virtual machines.
- Worked with LAMP (Linux, Apache, MySQL (database), Perl and Python) and Content Delivery Network (CDN).

Arabia marketing. Co.

Web Application Developer

03/2021 - 03/2023

- Developed full-stack web applications which processed, analyzed, maintain and rendered data visually.
- Planned, wrote, and debugged web applications and software with complete accuracy.
- Collaborate with more external programmers to create 2 more apps which

- connected to each other through our back-end.
- Managed, optimized, and updated our database as necessary.

PIVATE PROJECT

Fluxion - MITM WPA phishing

05/2019 - Present

- Design a system to retrieve the WPA/WPA2 key from a target access point.
- · Translate pages into the Arabic language.
- Testing various of wireless card for pen-testing.

Cardy - Digital business card

01/2022 - Present

- · Design the API and the back-end
- working on the front-end with modern framework like Vue and Svelte

SKILLS

Tech support ●●●●

UI/UX ●●●●

Software engineering ● ● ● ●



- Computer: Proficient in Windows and Linux OS, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, and Excel
- · Database: A good knowledge in SQL and MySQL database. I had experience in setting up Firebase, PostgreSQL and supabase database.
- Hosting: Worked with AWS and Microsoft Azure. Setup a Apach and nginx servers.
- Technology: React Hooks, GraphQL, Node.js, SQL, Postgres, NoSql, Redis, REST API, Git.
- Soft: Teamwork, Creative Problem Solving, Communication, Learning Mindset, Agile.